College of Humanities and Social Sciences Records 1913-1999 1960-1989
Carnegie Mellon University
- Publications/Books, This Series is arranged in the following Subseries by Department of origin: English History
  - History
    - Publications--"Communications in Business and Industry"
    - Publications—"Psychology"
    - Publications--"Carnegie Mellon Graduates 1985"
    - Publications--"Carnegie Mellon Graduates 1986"